<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<FIELDS>
	<FIELD name='st_subline'><TEXT/></FIELD>
	<FIELD name='st_headline'><TEXT>Individual Services</TEXT></FIELD>
	<FIELD name='st_accordion'><CATALOG><CARD id="702206cc-a60d-46db-9dc8-70bdc4a2ae03" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="§" set="1"><TEXT>24 HOUR HOTLINE SUPPORT</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="§" set="1"><DOM><p>After installation, you benefit from extensive SMART LIVING advantages: No matter when a question arises about your system, our 24-hour hotline is at your disposal. Our technically trained staff take care of your concerns around the clock and are happy to help you with any questions.</p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD><CARD id="f6b0011c-8510-45d4-b2f1-d9832d7f9cda" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="§" set="1"><TEXT>CONFIGURATION</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="§" set="1"><DOM><p>Sometimes preferences change: our knowledgeable staff can also assist you in reconfiguring your SMART LIVING solution. You have access to many sample configurations for a wide range of requirements and are happy to advise you. Just try it!</p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD><CARD id="830dea71-885f-42c8-b44d-5ed6d9f1ff16" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="§" set="1"><TEXT>PORTAL AND APP</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="§" set="1"><DOM><p>All preferences are also available on our service portal - there you can easily and directly change your individual settings. You will receive your credentials with your registration data. Extra tip: Download the free SMART LIVING app to easily change your configurations when and where you want them.</p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD><CARD id="6334f512-7eb0-4a74-9fcb-1ef72fcfd2b3" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="§" set="1"><TEXT>REGULAR UPDATES AND MAINTENANCE</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="§" set="1"><DOM><p>SMART LIVING as your smart home partner, is also responsible for keeping your software up to date. We regularly check the systems used for your safety and install any necessary updates immediately. And should an important component fail - no problem. We will provide spare parts in a timely manner.</p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD></CATALOG></FIELD>
</FIELDS>