<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<FIELDS>
	<FIELD name='st_subline'><TEXT>Everything you always wanted to know - answers to the most frequently asked questions</TEXT></FIELD>
	<FIELD name='st_headline'><TEXT>Frequently Asked Questions</TEXT></FIELD>
	<FIELD name='st_accordion'><CATALOG><CARD id="dcfdc21e-fdb7-4c28-9792-b9bda33fbbaf" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="ยง" set="1"><TEXT>Smart Home - What exactly is a smart home?</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="ยง" set="1"><DOM><p>It doesn't matter where you live - whether it's an old building or a new dream house: your home should be cozy, sustainable, comfortable, economical, energy-efficient and, above all, usable for a very long time.</p><p>Reconciling these goals - that's what we at SmartLiving are committed to. We offer you services and products that are optimally coordinated and intuitive to use.</p><p>Your smart home thinks and acts like you: It knows your needs and reacts to preferences, weather, living conditions and presence. It's the smart home that handles repetitive tasks for you, so you have more time to live.</p><p>Your smart home knows what you want. Which lighting you prefer when cooking, playing or relaxing; what music you prefer to listen to and what temperature is the most comfortable and efficient in the individual rooms.</p><p>This is comfort that borders on luxury - with products and services from SmartLiving.</p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD><CARD id="f7d85806-d33d-4ba5-8734-13f5211825db" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="ยง" set="1"><TEXT>How does a smart home work?</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="ยง" set="1"><DOM><p>A smart home usually consists of the following components:</p><p><ul><li><b>Actuators</b>: For example, lighting, radiator thermostats, blinds, and ventilation systems, but also media devices such as TVs and stereo systems or loudspeakers. Modern washing machines, dishwashers and stoves can now also be integrated into a smart home.</li><li><b>Input devices</b>: If you want a change, just click on a switch. Or a tap on the smartphone. Or a voice instruction. According to your wishes and preferences.</li><li><b>Sensors</b>: These are used, for example, to measure the room temperature. In addition, it can be determined whether windows or doors have been opened or whether people are present.</li></ul></p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD></CATALOG></FIELD>
	<FIELD name='st_info'><DOM/></FIELD>
</FIELDS>