<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<FIELDS>
	<FIELD name='st_subline'><TEXT>What you always wanted to know - answers to the most frequently asked questions</TEXT></FIELD>
	<FIELD name='st_headline'><TEXT>Frequently Asked Questions</TEXT></FIELD>
	<FIELD name='st_accordion'><CATALOG><CARD id="7af9fe5a-e458-421c-83a1-51f7cd56bda5" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="§" set="1"><TEXT>Smart Home - What exactly is a smart home?</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="§" set="1"><DOM><p>No matter where you live, whether an older building or a new dream home, your home should be cozy, sustainable, comfortable, economical, energy-efficient, and above all yours and dependable for as long as you need.</p><p>Reconciling these goals - that's what we at SmartLiving are committed to. We offer you services and products that are optimally coordinated and intuitive to use.</p><p>Your smart home thinks and acts like you, it knows your needs and reacts to your preferences, tracks the weather, living conditions, and whether someone is home. It's the smart home that can handle repetitive things for you, giving you more time to enjoy your home.</p><p>Your smart home learns what you want, like what lighting you prefer when cooking, playing or relaxing, which music you listen to, and what temperature is the most pleasant and efficient in each room.</p><p>This is comfort that borders on luxury, with products and services from SmartLiving.<br/></p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD><CARD id="bc37ede0-af7b-4a80-8619-c7b909cfcdab" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="§" set="1"><TEXT>How does a smart home work?</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="§" set="1"><DOM><p>A smart home usually consists of the following components:</p><p><ul><li><b>Actuators</b>: These devices can control lighting, thermostats, blinds, and ventilation systems. They can also manage media devices like TV and stereo systems or loudspeakers. In the meantime, modern washing machines, dishwashers and stoves can also be integrated into a smart home</li><li><b>Input devices</b>: If you need a change in the mood, the click of a switch, a tap on the smartphone, a simple voice command is all you need</li><li><b>Sensors</b>: Can be used for things like maintaining a room's temperature. They can also determine if windows or doors have been opened and whether people are present</li></ul></p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD><CARD id="2f48a935-ce86-4f95-9890-bb024b3ce41b" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="§" set="1"><TEXT>Why do I need a smart thermostat?</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="§" set="1"><DOM><p>Smart thermostats offer a variety of advantages compared with classic thermostats. For example, they can be used to save energy by automatically adapting to your daily routine and habits and regulate the temperature in your home accordingly.</p><p>Many smart thermostats also offer the ability to control the temperature from your smartphone or other mobile device. This means you can adjust the temperature in your home even when you are not at home.</p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD><CARD id="9a697ba0-16a0-47e0-a394-5e62c71ae104" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="§" set="1"><TEXT>Which smart home products are best for getting started?</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="§" set="1"><DOM><p>A good smart home product for getting started is a smart socket that can control and automate devices like lamps, televisions, or coffee makers with an app.</p><p>There are also many bundles that include several smart devices such as an electrical outlet, light bulbs, or motion sensors.</p><p>With these, you can easily take your first steps in the world of the smart home and find out which possibilities and functions make the most sense for your needs.</p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD><CARD id="5d49b089-0abd-4c86-b920-bc39058d5dd0" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="§" set="1"><TEXT>How can I save energy using smart home appliances?</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="§" set="1"><DOM><p>Are you looking to <b>save energy,</b> decrease your footprint and cost of living?</p><p>Here are a few ways a smart home can support you:</p><p><ul><li><b>Smart thermostats</b> automatically control the temperature in each room, lowering it when you are not home and increasing it when you are about to return, or based on a set schedule</li><li><b>Smart windows</b> can turn off heating and air-conditioning as soon as a window is opened</li><li><b>Smart sockets </b>decrease the energy consumption of devices that are on stand-by</li><li><b>Motion sensors </b>can automatically provide lighting when and where it is needed, saving energy</li></ul></p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD><CARD id="d31ace80-7832-452a-bd3f-3c9b6ce2ecec" template="accordion_item" type="TEMPLATESTORE"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="st_title"><LANG id="§" set="1"><TEXT>Do the smart home devices also work with voice control?</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="st_content"><LANG id="§" set="1"><DOM><p>Many smart home devices can be controlled using voice control systems such as Amazon's Alexa, Google Assistant, or Apple's Siri.</p><p>To do this, the devices must first be connected to the corresponding voice control system, for example the central Smart Home Hub or a special app.</p><p>After that, they can then be controlled with voice commands, like "Alexa, turn on the lights in the living room," or "Hey Siri, turn the heat up two degrees."</p><p>The exact commands depend on the device used and the voice control system.</p></DOM></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CARD></CATALOG></FIELD>
	<FIELD name='st_info'><DOM><p>Still have questions <CMS_LINK linktemplate="internal_link" type="genericLink"><TEMPLATECONTENT><CMS_VALUE name="lt_link"><LANG id="§" set="1"><UID>google_maps</UID><UIDTYPE>SITESTORE_LEAF</UIDTYPE><REMOTE/></LANG></CMS_VALUE><CMS_VALUE name="lt_text"><LANG id="§" set="1"><TEXT>Contact us</TEXT></LANG></CMS_VALUE></TEMPLATECONTENT></CMS_LINK></p></DOM></FIELD>
</FIELDS>